What's with that ship?
That weird movement and rapid-fire
magic cannon has to mean...
Yes... It takes into consideration
the brain's ability from the start.
That ship was made purely for war.
Commander! Port side Territory
has reached the threshold!
Redeploy Territory!
Hurry and recharge Mistilteinn!
Affirmative!
Kannazuki.
Roger!
Commander, now!
Right... Mistilteinn, fire!
That woman's got some nerve!
Goetia approaching!
Rest assured.
Using Yggdrafolium Territory to
bend the trajectory... Impressive.
I'm honored.
I couldn't let our beautiful World Tree
get damaged. Besides...
Besides?
Instead of getting attacked,
I like when you do the attacking!
Ugh...
Commander! Goetia's coming this way!
Hey! Anyone?!
Is anyone there?!
Shit, I don't have time for this!
O-Origami?
You came back for me?
By taking the life of Tohka Yatogami,
I will regain who I was.
Don't tell me, you...
An unbreakable vow of revenge...
Once again, the girl takes a step into hell.
O-Origami?
"Episode Seven:
'The Power Given'"
Look at that face! That face!
So funny! It hurts!
U-Um...
Shido.
Yoshino!
Are you okay, Shido?
Wow, nice job getting abducted there!
C'mon, Yoshino. Now's your chance
to have your way with Shi--
Wait, Yoshino!
Origami's dangerous! She's not normal!
--Um, don't you think that's enough?
--Ah, it hurts!
Eh?
N-Natsumi?!
What gives? Complaining already?
Not happy to see me?
No, but... Why are you two here?
Um, I was showing Natsumi around the city.
We saw you and Origami together.
And, well, Yoshino couldn't
let it go, so we followed you.
Natsumi! You promised not to say that!
--Anyways, this is great!
--Did I now?
--Gosh, I'm so embarrassed!
--Please, can you get me
out of these cuffs and rope?
--Gosh, I'm so embarrassed!
-Uh, sorry! Sorry about that, Yoshino!
So be it. You'll have to leave this to me.
Uh, but how?
Natsumi?
Shut up, you little shits!
Natsumi? What were you...?
I realized, whenever I
remember a bad feeling,
I somehow get back a bit of my power.
A bad feeling?
Yeah, like during school lunch...
I had no friends, so I was eating
lunch alone in a bathroom stall.
But I completely forgot to lock the door...
...and a girl from my class
found me eating inside.
That would be embarrassing...
And when I went back to class,
everyone was staring at me,
snickering and laugh--
Th-That's enough! Shall we get outta here?!
I can't reach Fraxinus...
Do you know where Tohka
and the others are at?
Tohka, are you finally awake?
Miku!
Origami Tobiichi!
You bastard! Why would you do this?!
I don't understand the question.
You're Spirits.
Calamities who ruin the world.
Beings which curse humanity.
That alone is answer enough.
Don't make me say it again.
Yuzuru!
An... guish. Master Origami... Why?
You bastard!
Get your hands off of Yuzuru, Origami!
Kaguya!
It took so long...
But now I've obtained it.
The power to kill Spirits...
The power to fulfill my wish!
With this strike, I'll regain who I was.
Soon, all the Spirits will
be killed by my hand!
So that never again will
a human like me be born!
Origami Tobiichi!
I can't even take a step forward,
let alone move an inch!
At this rate...
More... If only I had more power!
I can't! With that power,
I won't be able to save anyone.
I have to fight without losing who I am!
To save Kaguya...
To help Yuzuru...
To see Miku live!
And also... for her!
Shido! Lend me more power!
That form is...
Origami Tobiichi...
I hate you.
That hasn't changed one bit.
But this hate and the hate of the past...
are somewhat different.
So... I come to kill you!
Don't you die, Origami!
I've got this!
We're evenly matched!
With the power of this Mordred...
I can face the Spirit that killed
my mom and dad! And then...!
Activation limit...
Evenly matched, my ass...
I wasted my whole life...
all spent chasing a Spirit's power...
Since then, I've sacrificed
everything, yet...
Now I have nothing... left...
I...
Hey, do you wish for more power?
What are you?
Answer me. Do you wish for more power?
Absolute power... Power enough
to outmatch anyone.
I... want power.
No matter what it takes.
No matter the sacrifice.
If it's enough power to fulfill
my wish once and for all...
If I could have power such that
no one else can compare...
...I want it!
This is...?
If you want power, reach out your hand.
I'll give it to you.
That was...?
What's this about?
Substantial spirit waves.
It's a reading that wasn't in the DEM report.
Seriously? You mean another Spirit appeared?
What's more, no spatial quake either...
A silent appearance?
Wasn't Origami's so-called suspension
fixed by the DEM, too?
What in the world are they thinking?
Tohka, that look...
Yeah. When I knew I had to
save everyone, my power came back.
Ques... tion. Tohka, where's Master Origami?
I smacked her good with the flat of my sword.
That won't kill her.
She's got something called
"Teriyaki" protecting her body.
Teriyaki?
Correction. You mean Territory?
Miku!
We should thank her when she wakes up.
While you were fainted,
she defended you with her life.
Agreement. She was admirable.
Yeah... Thank you, Miku.
Yeah, yeah. You should try
waking her up then.
Hmm? What should I do?
Isn't it obvious?
To wake a sleeping princess,
you have to give her a big wet smooch.
A-A smooch?
Affirmative. That's right.
Now, go ahead and dive in.
Kiss! Kiss!
Hold on! I didn't say nothing!
Agreement. Me either.
Wh-What?
Miku! You're awake, aren't you?!
Aww, you found me out?
I was so close, too!
--You jerk! Imitating me is a grave offense!
--Scorn. Good grief!
So sorry! Please forgive me!
I promise I'll pay you
both back! With my body!
That's...
Origami?!
Confirmation. You think so, too?
It has to be... But, that form is...
Run.
Tohka!
I can't both protect and fight.
Tohka, sorry!
Prayer. Fight well!
Tohka Yatogami
I will... defeat you!
Origami, you little..!
Metatron!
You bastard! Why are you a Spirit?!
Spirit?
In that case...
This changes nothing.
I will wield this power
to defeat all Spirits!
I'll be a Spirit-killing Spirit.
And then, once I exterminate all Spirits,
I'll eradicate the only one left, myself!
Metatron, Shemesh!
Shido, look over there!
Is that them?!
What a monster...
Mal'akh!
Kadour!
Origami, I'll ask you one more time!
Can we not see eye to eye?
Don't be ridiculous!
My resolve will not change.
My mission will not change.
Every last Spirit I will not permit!
I see...
Then I have no choice.
Prepare yourself, foolish child!
I will punish you!
I've heard enough of your bullshit!
Sandalphon, Halvanhelv!
Metatron, Artelif!
Stop it!
Shido!
Why, you two?! Why are you doing this?!
Tohka! Origami!
Origami!
I did this...
I'm a Spirit,
but...
The me now can finally kill Spirits.
Not just Tohka Yatogami either...
But even Ifrit and Nightmare, too.
Could it be...?
What if doing that was possible?
I see. Origami became a Spirit...
No, I don't know all the details.
By the time she came back, she was already...
You should be resting!
Um, are you okay?
Wow, you really took a beating!
Nah, I'm fine!
Sigh. Kaguya is faking.
Shaddap! I'm perfectly fine! Ow, ugh...
I'm so ugly, worthless,
and dirty like trash...
But trash can be recycled,
so I'm worse than trash...
She used a bunch of her
power doing first aid...
Ow, ow, ow...
Miku? Don't push yourself!
I'm glad you're worried for me, Darling.
But, as long as I have power,
I still have a job to do.
A job?
Gabriel, Requiem!
Ladies and gentlemen!
Welcome to tonight's special show!
Miku Izayoi, on stage!
Wonder. My pain is fading away...
It's a song for pain relief.
Not that it accomplishes much...
Thanks, Miku.
I know! Let's get you to the hospital
while the song's working.
Can you walk, Tohka?
I have to seal her, don't I?
If the AST detect her,
they might sound the alarm...
What's wrong, Shido?
Uh, nothing!
Got a sec?
Shido? What are you doing?
U-Uh, you see...
O-Oh...
So, right here... we have to... do that?
U-Um... Well, it seems that way.
Shido...
I can't see anything!
Shh! Be quiet!
Could you stop moving?
Where'd Shido go?
You guys...
Hmm? Itsuka and Yatogami?
M-Ms. Tammie!
Whoa! What a hideous injury!
Eh?
You need the hospital, not the infirmary!
I'll go make the call!
My, my. What a strange
customer we have tonight.
Long time no see, Origami.
"Episode Eight:
'Demon King of Descending Darkness'"